

PLSQL Developer seeking roles in Software Engineering, Software Development, Project Management, Change Management, Incident Management, Escalation Management, Order Management, Technical Support, Debugging, Shell Scripting, Share Point, Eclipse, Rally



Current Designation: PLSQL Developer Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)

Current Company: TCS Notice Period: 3 Months

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: PLSQL/Software Developer, Software Engineering, Software Development, Project Management, Change Management, Incident Management, Escalation Management, Order Management, Technical Support, Debugging, Shell

Scripting, Share Point, Eclipse, Rally

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

2 years of experience in Oracle Apps (Order Management) Technical Support.

1+ year of experience in Treasury Cash management Team (Development).

Good knowledge of SQL and PL/SQL, working knowledge in Oracle database (R12).

Good knowledge in stored procedures, views, cursors and schema, Perl, shell scripting.

Expertized in Data Analysis Quarter wise.

Experience in first level escalation handling.

Responsible to apply change management processes throughout service request life cycle.

Direct interaction with clients and internal stakeholders

Working in fast paced environment where we need to maintain SLA's.

3+ years of SQL Server knowledge (Toad)

Have led the migration process from TES to CTM.

Work Experience

TCS as PLSQL Developer Aug 2016 to Till Date

Project Title: Treasury Cash management Flow

Client Cisco Organization TCS

Role Developer Module PL/SQL, shell, Perl scripting.

Duration April 2019 to Present Environment Enterprise Application Services (IOU)

Client Description:

Cisco Systems, Inc. is an American multinational technology conglomerate headquartered in San Jose, California, in the center of Silicon Valley. Cisco develops, manufactures and sells networking hardware, telecommunications equipment and other high-technology services and products. Through its numerous acquired subsidiaries, such as OpenDNS, WebEx, Jabber and Jasper, Cisco specializes into specific tech markets, such as Internet of Things (IoT), domain security and energy management.

Project Description:

Enhance the company's global cash flow and economic value, while helping Cisco achieve business objectives

- * Manage the Company's financial and non-financial risks in a prudent and cost effective manner
- Develop leading edge financing solutions which help sustain the Company's global growth and competitiveness
- * Promote shareholder value creation across the Company

Responsibilities/ Contributions:

Follows the Agile Process - Involved in Development, Unit Testing and Production release.

Handled user stories, Job monitoring, incident management.

I have led the job migration from TES to CTM. (Includes Creating new jobs, testing, prod push)

Creating the Knowledge documents (Functionality) and Periodic Knowledge Transition.

Involved in development of CCMC (Cisco Cash Management Central) using PI/SQL, Shell and Perl script.

Project Title: Order Management

Client Cisco Organization TCS

Role Support Executive. EAS ORACLE Module Oracle Apps

Duration April 2017 to 2019 Environment Enterprise Application Services (IOU)

Client Description:

Cisco Systems, Inc. is an American multinational technology conglomerate headquartered in San Jose, California, in the center of Silicon Valley. Cisco develops, manufactures and sells networking hardware, telecommunications equipment and other high-technology services and products. Through its numerous acquired subsidiaries, such as OpenDNS, WebEx, Jabber and Jasper, Cisco specializes into specific tech markets, such as Internet of Things (IoT), domain security and energy management.

Project Description:

ERP Order Management:

Order management is simply the process of efficiently tracking and fulfilling sales orders. It includes the cycle of people, processes, and suppliers to create a positive customer experience.

It uses ERP system, it's a fully integrated business management system covering functional areas of an enterprise like Logistics, Production, Finance, Accounting and Human Resources.

It's based on O2C cycle (Order to Cash) process. Order to cash (OTC or O2C) is a set of business processes that involve receiving and fulfilling customer requests for goods or services.

Responsibilities/ Contributions:

? Worked on Incident management, Periodic Monitoring of our concurrent programs, alerts. Involved in Weekly CR activity Analysis.

Created PBI's for the respective Bugs in the system.

Creating the Knowledge documents (Functionality) and Periodic Knowledge Transition.

1 year have been worked in Functional Part (OM BIZ)

1+ year have been worked in Technical Part (OM IT)

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Siddaganga Institute of Technology, Tumkur in 2016

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
SQL, PL/SQL, Perl, shell scripting	
SQL Server, R12, Tidal, Toad, Oracle	
Eclipse, service now, SharePoint, Rally	

1/22/2021

DB cure, CTM dashboard, Tectia

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Telugu				
Kannada				

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent / Temporary

Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time